[{"answer": "It shouldn't take the risk of default to get folks in this town to work together and do their jobs.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "But at what cost?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "In an odd way, the president of the United States wins even though he loses.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Who else do you think can come out of this genuinely feeling it's been a good period for them?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "It's very simple, Piers.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What's your assessment of where we are with this deal?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, it's always wonderful to be with Gabby no matter -- no matter what opportunity you have to spend time with her.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "What was it like for you to be with the congresswoman?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "ARUSONE: Well, I mean she's in this rehab program for a reason.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "How would you describe her condition at the moment?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Well, on the way in and the way out, she just was emotional.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "What did she say to you?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that's flattering of you to say, but, you know, for Gabby it's day by day right now.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "So what -- what is her political aspiration now?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "You know, I think the finest hour actually took place back in 2009 when the Tea Party started and the uprising began.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Is this the Tea Party's finest hour?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "But my problem, I guess, Mark Meckler, is that it's very easy to run into government on a ticker that we want to cut spending.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Who -- wouldn't be asking their politicians if this is the appropriate next step to take?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "I think it's crazy that the other side calls us so many names.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Do you feel you're either of those things?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "To say it's within our own party is incorrect.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "So you have this division within your own party, don't you?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, that is a fact.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "And could we see a scenario potentially following that argument where you would support Barack Obama in the next election?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I'm sure John Boehner feels very frustrated and unappreciated.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "If you were John Boehner, how would you be feeling right now?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "The reason John Boehner didn't get more done was because unfortunately people like Dick Armey were out there sending out e-mails to groups of conservatives and -- and criticizing him, don't compromise with the president.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Hilary Rosen, do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there's nobody that I know that's a Tea Party activist in America that sees themselves as part of a political party.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "The Tea Party, by common consent, are the political winners in all of this, aren't they?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "You know, and you've got the major Republican presidential candidates who, if they had their way, would have brought the country into default.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "You've got to say that at the moment, who takes on Obama?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, quite frankly, my own view is that President Obama has demonstrated himself to be -- first of all, he's so ideologically defined, he virtually understands nothing but income redistribution, and he's incompetent at even doing that, to the frustration of the --", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Who stands right now?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "All of the above.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "However, what is the answer to my question, which is, which of all the candidates right now -- and there's a clear split ideologically between the Michele Bachmann end of things and the Mitt Romney end of things -- which of the candidates who have declared an interest so far do you believe could beat the president?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I think that no matter who they nominate, they're going to coalesce around the candidate and try and spend the billions of dollars to try and defeat the president.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "I mean, what would you say, Hilary?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "I wasn't surprised by what I heard.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "When you heard about what had happened, as somebody that concocts these outrageous plot lines yourself, were you surprised by what you heard?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Were you critical at all of the time it took the authorities there to get to that island?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "You would think so.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Well, my books -- I think one of the hallmarks of my thrillers is that they're based in reality.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "What is the plot here?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Steven King had a great line.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "What makes you, Brad Thor, an apparently normal guy, have these incredibly weird, random thoughts?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Well, I always joke around that the Red Cell Program is the Las Vegas of government programs.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Or happen?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "We got a lot of threats, which was not easy for me as a husband and father.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What was the fallout like for you personally after that?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "That for me was as great as it was -- being part of the Red Cell Program, that for me was a dream come true.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "What was that like?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110802pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Do you think it's a more dangerous world now than it was in 2001?", "qSentId": 545}]